You have to see it to belove it!
Pocketful of Miracles is a comedy, drama film directed by Frank Capra.
A New York gangster and his girlfriend attempt to turn street beggar Apple Annie into a
society lady when the peddler learns her daughter is marrying royalty.
Dave 'The Dude' Conway, played by Glenn Ford.
Apple Annie, played by Bette Davis.
Elizabeth 'Queenie' Martin, played by Hope Lange.
Count Alfonso Romero, played by Arthur O'Connell.
Joy Boy, played by Peter Falk.
Judge Henry G. Blake, played by Thomas Mitchell.
Pocketful of Miracles is a 1961 American comedy film, starring Glenn Ford and Bette
Davis, produced and directed by Frank Capra, filmed in Panavision.
The screenplay by Hal Kanter and Harry Tugend was based on Robert Riskin's screenplay for the 1933 film Lady
for a Day, which was in turn adapted from the 1929 Damon Runyon short story "Madame La Gimp".
That original 1933 film was also directed by Capra—one of two films that he originally directed and
later remade, the other being Broadway Bill (1934) and its remake Riding High (1950).
The film was the final project for both Capra and Thomas Mitchell.
It marked Ann-Margret's film debut.
Peter Falk was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.
The film explores themes of new york city,
prohibition era, gangster, deception, apple.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.